(Howard:)So two years later,
there's a knock on the door.
Guy opens it, and there is the snail...
(Howard:)...who says,
"What the heck was all that about?"
[CHUCKLES]
(Bernadette:)I don't really get it.
(Howard:)Well, see, it took two years
for the snail to--
(Howard:)Not important.
(Bernadette:)-Can I ask you a question?
-Sure.
(Bernadette:)Where do you think this is going?
(Howard:)To be honest,
I was hoping at least second base.
(Bernadette:)You're so funny.
(Bernadette:)You're like a standup comedian.
(Howard:)A Jewish standup comedian,
that would be new.
(Bernadette:)Actually, I think a lot of them
are Jewish.
No, I was just-- Because-- Never mind.
(Bernadette:)Look, Howard, this is our third date,
and we both know what that means.
(Howard:)-We do?
-Sex.
(Howard:)You're kidding.
(Bernadette:)But I need to know whether
you're looking for a relationship...
(Bernadette:)...or a one-night stand.
(Howard:)Okay, just to be clear,
there's only one correct answer, right?
I mean, it's not like "Chicken or fish?"
on an airplane?
(Bernadette:)Maybe you need to think about it
a little.
Well, you know, it's not unheard of...
(Howard:)...for a one-night stand
to turn into a relationship.
(Bernadette:)Call me when you figure it out.
(Howard:)Three dates means sex?
(Howard:)Who knew?
[TV PLAYING]
Greetings, homeys.
(Howard:)Homette.
(Penny:)Why are you back from your date
so early?
Well, in romance, as in show business,
always leave them wanting more.
(Penny:)-What exactly does that mean?
-He struck out.